<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="changelogcontent">
        <b>Please try to feedback at "Feedback" section, you can try to send anonmously if you don\'t have a Github account, it may let you feel anonying, but it will save me a lot of times. Thanks</b>\n
        \n
        <b>Version 1.0.4</b>\n
        \n
        - Fixed small bugs\n
        - Introducing a new color picking method -- "Phonograpg"\n
          note: this method is completely simulate phonograpg\'s picking method, which looks really good\n
        - Add Music Player\'s small icon in notification\n
          note: when you block nothing, Medianotification will get the player\'s small icon automatically. However, if you block the player's notification, Medianotification can only use local player icons. Now there are only 2 player\'s icon can be used:Cloud Music and Phonograph. You can tell me the player\'s name so i can add it.\n
        - Now you can block Phonograph and Retro Music\'s notification in SystemUI because Medianotification is fully support these two players.\n
          note: Unfortunately you can not block Cloud Music in SystemUI now, because Cloud Music changed too many things and i haven\'t found a suitble way to judge its situation. Please be paient and i will find it one day.\n
          Also, players which do not use Android API like Tencent QQ music or Poweramp are now not supported at all. I am very sorry.\n
        - Broadcast is now working, you won\'t listen to the next music when you press "Play" button ant more.\n
        - Fixed a broadcast bug which leads to the wrong keycode\n
        - Fixed Bitmap error\n
        - Synced translation\n
        \n
        \n
        \n
        <b>Version 1.0.3</b>\n
        \n
        - Fixed a lots of bugs\n
        - Make app can fetch arts from Tencent Music\n
        - Add more helps\n
        - Translate "Feedback" section\n
        - Add a github token to let you feedback annoymously\n
        - Auto crop and scale the art when the art is too long\n
        - Improve color picking performance\n
        - Try to fix the problem that the Cloud Music Player shuts down automatically\n
        - Links to Tencent Bugly Plantform to collect bugs and logs\n
        - Sync translation\n
        \n
        \n
        \n
        <b>Version 1.0.2</b>\n
        \n
        - Add raditional Chinese traslation support\n
        - Add Bug reporter to help report to Github\n
        - Fixed some bugs\n
        \n
           ATTENTION:It turned out that after API24,notification cannot expand itself,but need users to expand it manually.so i cannot make it always expand.
        \n
        - Add helps\n
        - Add 2 method to daemon\n
        - Learning Xposed...
        \n
        \n
        \n
        <b>Version 1.0.1</b>\n
        \n
        - Add Chinese traslation support\n
        - Optimize color algorithms\n
        - Optimize logic\n
        - Add more helps\n
        - Add Intro Activity\n
        \n
        \n
        \n
        <i>From now on,Medianotification that uploaded to Coolapk Market will be under my maintain.Thanks for everybody\'s support.</i>\n
        <i>When you have a good idea or find a bug,please reported to my Github but not Coolapk Market\'s comment area,which will make it difficult to trace and fix.</i>\n
        <i>However,if you dont have a Github account,then you can only post your idea in comment area,but dont forget to @me</i>\n
        <i>You can find my github URL at "help"</i>\n
        \n
        \n
        <b>Version 1.0.0</b>
        \n
    </string></resources>